♪
[UKA] I can't keep writing
things off as beyond my depth.
-[plane whirring]
-I'll try anything I can.
I volunteer.
Please, let me!
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[TONBO]
You're volunteering?
[MIRU]
You, actually want to be
-on the committee?
-[SATORU] Like, for real?
-[KAMAKIRI] My hero!
-[TAO] Totally works for me.
-[TAO] Ishimori's smart.
-[TONBO] Yeah,
though she doesn't get "vibes."
[MIRU]
What do you think, Kai?
Why would you be asking me?
[MIRU] Well,
you're like, her caretaker
or something, aren't ya?
Hmm.
Hmph.
-[Uka gasps]
-[KAI] Can you handle it?
Uh-huh.
'Cause you can't just quit.
I won't.
Gotta see it through
to the end.
-I will!
-[KAMAKIRI] Sounds like
she's in!
[YUKINO]
What are we gonna do?
-[MIRU] A manga cafe!
-[TONBO] Haunted house!
[AYUMI]
You got this, Ishimori!
[chuckles]
[UKA]
I won't let them down!
It'll be tough,
but I'll pull this off!
Everybody's counting on me!
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6A]
All right, people, make sure
the tarp is down,
and be on your way!
-Lots to do, so no napping!
-Oh, you're on the committee?
[UKA'S MOM]
Oh, that's wonderful!
What's your theme?
[UKA]
A cafe,
if the student council
gives their approval.
[UKA'S DAD]
I wish I didn't have to work.
I'd love to grab a bite
at your cafe.
[beeps]
[panting]
Seems like you're having
a lot of fun lately, huh?
Mm. I am, yeah!
[UKA]
It's true.
I feel there's finally a place
where I belong.
And I've got support
from the whole class!
[panting]
[whimpering]
[screaming]
[thuds]
[gasps]
What's with all the rush?
[UKA]
Oh. It's you!
Where's everyone else?
[UKA]
Well, I just thought
I'd get all the stuff
we need myself.
[KAI]
Oh, yeah?
Maybe we could've been cooler
about all that.
[TAO]
Cooler to Ishimori?
Like, the plan so far
was just "a cafe."
So why should we bust our butts
collecting boxes and stuff?
-[NAGANO] I know, right?
-I don't wanna
do some stupid maid cafe.
[SHIRAISHI] Well, then,
why did you raise your hand?
[NAGANO]
I hated the other ideas more,
so, process of elimination.
Huh?
[both groan]
-[TAO] Not cool.
-[SHIRAISHI] Not cool.
[TAO]
The reason she didn't throw
a single suggestion out there
was just so she could bitch
about all of it later.
[SHIRAISHI]
So typical.
Hey, now.
Pretty big talk for someone
who flat out
refused to help at all.
I wanna do a cafe.
Our class is just selling baked
goods from the grocery.
I still can't believe
you guys won.
[ALL]
Huh?
What did we win?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6A] Every class
wanted to do a cafe.
But Ishimori got up
in front of everyone
and unveiled this super
detailed plan for it.
And she was like,
"I know our class can do
a great job with it."
Of course, she was shaking
like a leaf the entire time.
[both groan]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6A]
Sucks for us.
[all groan]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6B]
A maid cafe would be cute!
[all groan]
[KAI]
They said no, huh?
[UKA]
Yeah. Sorry.
I guess I still haven't
learned to "vibe" yet.
[KAI]
So what?
It's not like you have to,
or anything.
I'm confused.
You're probably the only person
who'd say that to me.
[KAI]
'Cause I'm an idiot.
I wanna know what's your
definition of "idiot?"
[birds chirping]
[KAI]
Someone who breaks the rules.
But whose rules
are you breaking?
Adults' and all the people
who suck up to 'em.
♪
[birds chirping]
[KAI]
What's that look about?
I'm just listening.
So, you decided you'd live
by your own rules?
Sure, in a twisted way.
[UKA]
If I had to choose between
living by the adults'
rules or yours,
I'd pick yours.
I'm sure that everyone
you know would, too.
[sighs]
[KAI]
I'm not some kinda God.
Just a stupid punk.
[UKA]
You're unique.
That's why
when you always guide me
in a different direction,
it still feels right.
You give me advice
I wouldn't get from any adult.
[KAI] Crap.
I gotta bail.
Don't worry about my rules.
You make the rules now.
That's what committee
members do, right?
[plane whirring]
[sighs]
[beeping]
[panting]
[whimpering]
[screaming]
[thuds]
[whimpering]
-[eagles screeching]
-[breathing heavily]
[UKA]
What am I even doing?
Oh, no, what happened to you?
You okay? Can you move?
[UKA]
She's sweating?
[SHIRAISHI] How far do we
have to carry these boxes?
-Oh, and uh, where are we
going? -Can we see your plan?
We're sorry about before.
We promise to help you.
That's right.
We'll work together.
[UKA] No one's ever talked
to me like this.
Not even my parents.
[TAO]
You are okay, right?
[SHIRAISHI] If you're hurt,
we'll take you to see
the nurse.
No problem!
[NAGANO]
We don't mind.
[all laugh]
[KAI] Gotta see it
through to the end.
You make the rules now.
[UKA]
Yeah.
I know I can do it.
Everything will work out.
All those clouds have
cleared away.
[airplane whirring]
[MALE STUDENT 6A]
Ugh, I'm so hungry!
All right. It's time for us
to make some decisions
on the menu!
CLASS 1-B CULTURE
FESTIVAL PROJECT PLAN
[gasps] Do we read
the whole thing, or...
Sorry, Ishimori.
It seems like you--
[grunting]
[MIRU]
Oh, crap.
[TONBO] She's
super fired up about this.
[Uka panting]
I can be assertive.
Our budget's 20,000 yen?
[YURU] What do you ladies
think about coming up
with some more pancake flavors?
[ASUMI]
Oh, now, you're into it?
Of course.
We wanna wow 'em, yeah?
Yeah, we do!
[chuckles]
A certain someone
told the student council
we would!
[YURU] We can't make Uka
a liar, can we?
Let's show 'em
what Class 1-B can do!
Hey. Don't get all teary eyed
just 'cause someone's
nice to you.
Kinda uncool.
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6A]
Why in the world are you
drawing a devil girl with big
tiger striped boots on?
I know for a fact
nobody asked for that!
[Uka panting]
[MOMO] So, uh, is it okay
to change the design?
[ALL]
Huh?
Pretty sure we could
pull it off
without needing so much fabric.
-But how to construct the bust?
-We just need 2 meters...
[UKA] I need to stop trying
to solve everything on my own
and put more faith
in the people around me.
...at 750.
[KAEDE] I've got some
petticoats I can donate!
[all groan]
-[beeping]
-[panting]
[YURU]
What'll we name the cafe?
[SHIRAISHI]
"Cafe 1-B" works for me.
[TAO]
Hmm, A bee. Abe.
Hey, "Avail" is a word
in English, right?
What's it mean, though?
[panting]
[TONBO] Are we gonna get
all this stuff done in time?
We've only got four
more days left to go!
Don't worry, guys!
We'll be fine!
-Huh? [groans]
[TONBO] Whoa, Ishimori!
You're ridin' the vibe!
[MIRU]
Yeah! Totally!
[TONBO]
Get it, Ishimori!
[UKA]
This is fun!
And it's all because
I'm not alone anymore!
[indistinct chatter]
[MALE STUDENT 6A]
Ugh! I'm starving!
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6A]
Then work faster!
-[AYUMI] Hey, Uka.
-[gasps]
You do remember me?
Please say yes.
[UKA] Ayumi! Of course,
I remember you.
We're all just so busy!
[AYUMI] We're dancing
to this Denpa girls' song
and it's killing me.
[SATORU] Ooh,
like for real, for real?
-[BOTH] Huh?
-[SATORU] Ya know,
now that I think about it,
you kinda look like Mog!
Man, I love her!
-[laughs]
-[AYUMI] Oh, I'm aware.
-[SATORU] Yeah, is that right?
-[gasps]
[laughing]
You have gotta be kidding me!
The whole reason
I cut my bangs is
because you wouldn't stop
talking about her!
-How are you such an idiot?
-[SATORU] Huh? Wait! Ayumi!
[SHIRAISHI] They're so gonna
hook up at the festival.
Well, you know that Satoru.
He's kind of a dense guy.
People always get together
at these things, though.
[UKA]
As for my love?
[ASUMI]
Yo, lumber, stat!
[UKA]
I'll go grab some!
♪
[UKA] Look at them.
They're perfect.
Like they're glowing.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[whimpering]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6C]
And, rolling!
I'm 1-C's Musashi Furuichi.
Always here for fun times!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6C]
Hang on. Who's that?
-Huh?
-[SERINA] Uka?
[SHIRAISHI]
Yeah, that's her!
Hey, Ishimori!
[YURU] Check out
how we set up the garlands!
[UKA]
Miura?
Life is bright with you. But...
[laughter]
[UKA]
It's just as bright here!
[MALE STUDENT 6B]
Who's that?
[MALE STUDENT 6C] That
Ishimori girl from Class 1-B.
Heard she was so boring
back in junior high
that she got bullied
all the time.
Aren't you supposed to be
helping her with that, Kai?
[MALE STUDENT 6B]
Wait, why him?
Is he in the same class?
[MALE STUDENT 6C] Yeah.
He's Ishimori's caretaker.
[SERINA] Hey, back off.
Don't make it sound like--
[MALE STUDENT 6C] Bet you wish
you were Kanno's
caretaker instead.
[Serina sighs]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6C]
Moving on. Kai's next!
And, rolling!
I'm from 1-B. Kai Miura.
[YURU] What were
they doing back there?
[SHIRAISHI]
It's called "Crazy Cool."
Just some bit where they pick
some hot people
from each grade and show 'em
off at the festival.
Apparently, it's all the rage.
[UKA] I wish I could be there
with the boy I love.
But I have to stay focused
on this, now.
♪
[UKA]
It starts tomorrow.
If only one thing works out,
let it be the cafe!
But if I could have two,
then...
I want to find time
to talk with Miura!
HACHIMITSU FESTIVAL
[MALE STUDENT VENDOR 6A]
Come to class 3-A
and get some okonomiyaki!
[ASUMI]
Wait. No way.
-[gasps]
-You drew this, Ishimori?
So good! I never knew
you were an artist!
Well, I spent a lot of time
drawing in junior high.
-I was always by myself.
-[NAGANO] Customers incoming!
♪
[MOMO] Please, sir,
what can I get you?
[MALE STUDENT 6D]
Let's see.
[MALE STUDENT 6E] Wow!
Look at all these pancakes!
[YUKINO]
There are seven flavors!
Please enjoy!
[MALE STUDENT 6F]
This ice cream rocks!
[NAGANO]
I'm glad it's to your liking.
♪
Oh, good. We're selling out!
-You're up!
-Huh?
-Come with me!
-[screams]
-Got her!
-You can't!
-No one wants to see me!
-Hey! Get her dress!
[TAO]
No complaining!
♪
I hate this.
But, hey...I'll give it
the best I've got.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6D]
Can I place an order?
-Coming!
-[MALE STUDENT 6G] Me too!
-Be right there!
-When you get the chance?
[bell dings]
[SHIRAISHI] Sorry for throwin'
that at you, Ishimori.
Take a load off!
I think I will.
-[UKA] Thank--
-[SHIRAISHI] Slow down, there.
Keep that on.
Huh.
Uh-uh. Back on maid duty.
No breaks.
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6B]
Attention, all festival goers!
We found a lost child!
If you are missing a boy
in a blue hat
named Sho, come to
the first-floor entrance.
[UKA]
This is nice.
It's like, for once
I'm alone
without feeling alone.
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6B]
Please pick him up
as soon as possible!
Crazy Cool's starting soon!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6G]
Hope we're not too late!
[CRAZY COOL NARRATOR 6A]
Welcome, beautiful people.
Now, let's delight in youth!
Just as bees love nectar,
we love the sweeter things
in life!
Let's go!
CRAZY COOL
[audience cheering]
[MUSASHI] I'm 1-C's
Musashi Furuichi.
[audience cheering]
[MUSASHI]
Always here for fun times!
[male student 6h laughs]
Go, Musashi!
[MALE STUDENT 6I] Sheesh!
Who're you trying to impress?
[SERINA]
From Class 1-E, Serina Kanno.
Here to make your heart pound.
[MALE STUDENT 6J]
Yeah! Serina!
[MALE STUDENT 6N]
What a Goddess!
[UKA]
Incredible.
She's even perfect on camera.
-[female student screams]
-Huh?
-[FEMALE STUDENT 6H] It's him!
-[FEMALE STUDENT 6I] Miura!
[KAI]
I'm from 1-B. Kai Miura.
Here for Ishimori.
♪
CLASS 1-B KAI MIURA
He's what? What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
[UKA]
How do I interpret that?
Actually, it makes
no difference what he meant.
No matter what,
it made me happy
[FEMALE STUDENT 6J]
Are you Ishimori?
That girl from Crazy Cool,
right?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6K]
What's up with you and Miura?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6L] For real.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6M]
We're waiting, here.
[gasps]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6K]
He your caretaker or something?
[UKA]
Oh, well...
That's what our classmates
call him.
-There it is.
-That's it.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6J]
To be clear, that means
when you grow up a little,
Miura can just throw you out?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6L] Not like
he gets anything from you!
-That's true.
-[chuckles]
[FEMALE STUDENT 6L]
Good for him!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6K]
At least, we know why
he said something so crazy.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6J]
We're fine!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6M]
Sorry! Later!
-[all students laugh]
-[UKA] They're right.
I can't believe
I didn't realize it before.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6J]
To be clear,
that means when you grow up
a little,
Miura can just throw you out?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6L] Not like
he gets anything from you!
[UKA]
He hangs out with me
because he feels like
he has to.
-My days with him are numbered.
-[door slides open]
[gasps]
[footfall]
There. Found you.
Why're you dressed like that?
Couldn't say no, huh?
[chuckles]
[UKA]
He's here?
[KAI]
Got it.
Been to the nurse?
[UKA] No, I'm okay.
Sorry to worry you.
You should take
a breather, okay?
♪
-I saw you.
-Huh?
[UKA]
On Crazy Cool.
Oh, yeah.
Wasn't surprising to anybody
who knows me.
[UKA]
I have him for now.
[airplane droning]
[UKA]
No. I want more.
I can be greedy.
It's okay!
I have to tell you!
Starting now,
I'm gonna initiate
more conversations with you!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6N]
I wonder if Miura's already
got a girl that he likes.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6O]
Maybe Ishimori?
[FEMALE STUDENT 6N]
The one he talked about?
Well, heard he's just trying
to stop people
from bullying her.
That sounds tough.
Well, duh,
no way a guy like him
would be into a total loser
like that.
[gasps]
♪
[door slides open]
-Huh?
[gasps]
[KAI]
So? Anything to say?
[UKA] Uh...
I'm kinda struggling, now.
[KAI]
Aw, c'mon.
[TOMOYA]
Kai.
You mind?
[UKA]
Go ahead.
[KAI] Didn't you say
you wanted to talk more?
[TOMOYA]
You're "here for Ishimori?"
Pick one.
If you're just gonna
push her away,
do it before she's
dependent on you.
Otherwise,
get ready to buckle down.
This isn't half as apocalyptic
as you're making it sound.
Not to you.
But what about to her, huh?
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6B]
Coming up next,
"Rock in Hachimitsu!"
Well, something to think about.
...head-to-head!
I'll see you there.
Don't miss it!
[UKA] He grabbed my hand
without me having to ask.
[FEMALE STUDENT 6J]
To be clear,
that means when you grow up
a little,
Miura can just throw you out?
[UKA] I am gonna
start initiating more.
Right up until he decides
he's done with me.
[audience cheering]
-It's him!
-Takamine's so cool!
[FEMALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 6B]
Ladies and gentlemen!
Hachimitsu83 is up!
[AUDIENCE] [chanting]
Yeah!
[SATORU]
Ayumi! Ayumi! Ayumi!
Ayumi! Ayumi! Ayumi! Ayumi!
[UKA]
Wow.
I never agreed
to something like this!
[MALE STUDENT OPERATIONS 6A]
Some of the guys are only
in it because of you!
Not my problem!
[MALE STUDENT OPERATIONS 6A]
Fine, then!
If you don't wanna do it,
find me someone who will!
[gasps]
So you expect me to find
my own replacement?
Would you let me go out
in her place?
-Huh?
-You sure about that?
-Yeah.
I can make all the other girls
look better by comparison!
[both gasp]
Don't talk like that. Girl.
It's all right, I'll be okay!
Uh?
[MALE MC 6A]
Welcome!
Now for the moment
you've waited for.
It's "Let's Couple Up!"
Let's see if we can witness
true love bloom today!
Now, our contestants
will all introduce themselves.
[UKA]
Do we have to?
I suck at that.
I wonder if Miura's
watching this.
I bet he'd be surprised.
Wait. Don't think about that.
I've gotta be able
to do something
without roping him in.
[MALE MC 6A]
Next up. Contestant 2!
I'm ready!
Well, well!
You're the famous Ishimori!
Rather different
than I would've thought.
Aren't ya?
[chuckles]
[MALE STUDENT 6K]
Get it together, emcee!
[MALE MC 6A]
You're right, sorry!
Look at you, legs for days!
[MALE MC 6A]
What's better than a quiet girl
with a body like this?
[MALE STUDENT 6K]
A lotta stuff!
[laughs]
[UKA] Is this another "vibe?"
-Am I supposed to laugh?
-[MALE MC 6A] Well,
don't judge a book
by its cover, lads!
[chuckles]
[MALE MC 6A] We've even
got the awkward laughter!
[UKA] I almost wish Serina
had done this.
Miura would be here
in a heartbeat.
[indistinct chatter]
[grunts]
[KAI] [groans]
What a pain.
[indistinct chatter]
It feels like I can't ever
turn my back on you!
[MALE MC 6A] What?
A last minute entrant?
Is Kai Miura joining?
What do you have to say?
[KAI] Sorry.
She's dropping out.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[whimpering]
Miura. Thank you.
I know that I would
have been okay without you,
but still...
[sniffling]
[UKA] I want to be close to you
while I can be.
[weeping]
So I want to be strong for you.
I'm with you.
[KAI]
Always.
[gasps]
[airplane droning]
♪
[TOMOYA]
If I recall,
you said you're not interested
in Uka like that.
[KAI]
Who cares what I said?
But since you keep asking,
I take it back.
[footfall]
♪
TO BE CONTINUED